(Leonard:)Excuse me, your entire argument
is predicated on the assumption...
(Leonard:)...that Superman's flight
is a feat of strength.
Are you listening to yourself?
(Leonard:)Superman's flight is a feat of strength.
(Sheldon:)An extension of his ability
to leap buildings...
(Sheldon:)...an ability he derives
from exposure to sun...
How does he fly at night?
(Sheldon:)A combination
of the moon's solar reflection...
(Sheldon:)...and the energy storage capacity
of Kryptonian skin cells.
I'm just gonna go wash up.
I have 2600 comic books in there.
(Leonard:)I challenge you to find a single reference
to Kryptonian skin cells.
(Sheldon:)Challenge accepted.
(Sheldon:)We're locked out.
(Raj:)Also, the pretty girl left.